Did you experience it?
経験できた?
Do you always masturbate?
いつもさ、オナニーとかしたりする?
Yes, I will.
うん、する
Are you going to do it?
するんだ?
So, can I have you do a live commentary of your masturbation like you always do?
じゃあ、 いつもしてるように オナニー実況してもらっていい?
Masturbation commentary?
オナニー実況?
How do you usually feel?
どんな感じにするの、いつも?
I usually watch AV.
いつもは AV見てる
Do you want to see it?
見るの?
So today, let's remember that AV and try it out with a little imagination.
じゃあ、今日は そのAVを思い出して ちょっと妄想でやってみ
hand.
て
Do you have a favorite?
お 気に入りのやつあるでしょ?
I'm a little concerned.
ちょっと気になるな
secret.
秘密
So, try it all the time.
じゃあ、いつもやってみて
Do you touch my chest?
胸とか触ったりする?
I might not even touch it.
あんま触んないかも
Won't you touch me?
あ んま触んない?
Are you touching the bottom?
下は触ってるりするんだ?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Today I'm lying down.
今日は、寝転がってる
Ah, that's what it is.
あ、そういうことね
before going to bed.
寝る前に
Lying face down?
うつ伏せ?
upwards.
上向きで
It's Kriege.
クリージって
Like that.
そんな感じで
After all, don't use toys or anything.
やっぱり おもちゃとかも使わないで
Oh, then are you going to touch it?
あ、 じゃあ触ったりするの?
I won't touch it anymore.
俺はもう触んない
A small one?
ちっちゃいやつ?
A small one.
ちっちゃいやつ
a,
あ、
That's how you touch your neck.
そう やって首触るんだ
Really, touch how you feel.
ほんと、自分の気持ちよに触って
Ah, it changes.
あ、変わるんだ
I'll do a lot.
いっぱいしちゃうよ
The butt is also a bit unexpected.
お尻もちょっとまさか
Looks like I'll be leaving soon.
すぐいっちゃいそう
I guess I'll go.
いっちゃうんだろ
You can say it.
いっていいよ
Then go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝ろよ
Breathe, tell me later.
息さ、後に教えてね
Did you go?
行 ったの?
Tell me, properly.
教えてよ、ちゃんと
Tell me next time.
次教えて
went?
行 った?
I always take my breath.
いつも息までするんだ
It's a personal situation.
個人状態じゃん